# Shreyas S Sreedhar

#### **UI/UX Designer**

shreyas-sreedhar.com linkedin.com/in/shreyas-sreedhar shreyas.sreedhar@gmail.com

I'm a Designer and a Developer, exploring interaction, data, and conversation to solve problems by merging my analytical and creative halves to make meaningful products and experiences. Currently, a Senior Year Computer Science Engineering student at Jyothy IT.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**UI/UX Intern** • Centre for eGovernance, Govt. of Karnataka April 2021 - June 2021

- » Worked with the team in Redesigning the Website by User interviews, Prototyping and user-tested Mahiti Kanaja, a Public Information Portal of the government of Karnataka.
- » Performed data-driven research on a small group to help understand the users and standardize visual design across the site and prototype new interactions and UI components.

#### Front-end Developer Intern • JyothyMediaWorks

May 2020 - July 2020

- » Created wire-frames, user flow diagrams and low fidelity prototypes and the Website User interfaces of JMW and JyothylCM.
- » Developed the UI using HTML, CSS and JS.

## Graphic Design Intern • Jyothy Institute of Technology

May 2018 - July 2020

- » Directed a team of 4 creating JIT's written and visual marketing strategy to strengthen our presence as the premier research and entrepreneurial based engineering college in Karnataka.
- » Defined college's brand guidelines and Bolstered brand's digital presence on social media.

### Freelancing • SSS Designs

2015 - 2021

- » Provided Digital 2D&3D renders for automotive vinyl wrapping companies under the brand SSS Wrapdesigns.
- » Designed print media and digital media with clients like WrapCraft, Selvitate, Carszpa Kleenweks, Endless Customs, DC Days, SuperbikesinBangalore & more over the years.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering

Jyothy Institute of Technology, Bangalore August 2017 - August 2021 (Expected)

#### SKILLS

#### Design

Wire framing • Rapid Protyping • Design Systems • Brand & Strategy • Value Proposition • Product Development • Affinity Diagramming • AR • VR • 3D

#### Tools

Figma • InVision • Spark AR • Adobe Creative Suite (Ps, Ai, Lr, Xd) • Blender

#### Development

HTML • CSS • JavaScript • Python • Java • PHP Solidity • React • SQL

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

**2nd Runners-up** — 24Hours Gameathon 3.0 Designed a 3D game under 24 hours with a team of 4

#### **PROJECTS**

**WIAS** — Wildlife Intelligence and Automated Security (Work in progress — Bachelor of Engineering Thesis)

**ExploreBangalore** — Augmented Reality App Concept

### Pranathi Fest Registration Management System

-Intuitive Participant Admission Dashboard for college fests